ACTWU's Legal Department Records 5619/017
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Statements, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 72-2045 [folder 1 of 2], 1972 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 72-2045 [folder 2 of 2], 1972 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Statements - Organizing Committee, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 28-RC-2054 [folder 1 of 2], 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 28-RC-2054 [folder 2 of 2], 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Farah - ULP 28-CA-2036 Briefs to TX [folder 1 of 2], 1972 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Farah - ULP 28-CA-2036 Briefs to TX [folder 2 of 2], 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. (FP) Bill Patterson Records [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. (FP) Bill Patterson Records [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. (FP) Complaints, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Farah Pittsburgh (FP) Notices of Depositions, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. (FP) Interoffice Memoranda, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Pittsburgh Lawsuit, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Press Kit, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. (FP) Retailer Letters, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Securities and Exchange Commission, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Union Label Department Records (Originals) [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Union Label Department Records (Originals) [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. (FP) Union Label Filed Records, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Consumer Education Campaign, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 23-CA-4435, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. General [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  1972 to October 1973
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. General [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  1972- October 1973
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. General [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. General [folder 2 of 2], 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. The Advance, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. New Charges, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Statements - Organizing Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Statements for Joel, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 22-CC-462 & 22-CC-472, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Ponsford Case, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. General, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Stewarts Dry Goods / Rodes Rapier, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Sage-Allen / Jack's Dept. Store / Art Jones, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Korvettes, New York, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Hecht's Washington, DC, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Wiebolts, Chicago, Ill., 1973 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Patrick James Campbell City, San Fran, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Hudson's Detroit, Mich, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. El Paso, Texas Case No. 28-CC-462, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 8(B)(7) Material, 1968-1972 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Organizing Committee, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. ----I, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Extra Copies 23-CA-4389 Petitioners Exceptions & Briefs, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Picketing 8(B)(7) Problems, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Players Association, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Damages Materials Prepmore Case [folder 1 of 3], 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Damages Materials Prepmore Case [folder 2 of 3], 1966-1968 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Damages Materials Prepmore Case [folder 3 of 3], 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Proffitts Dept. Store Alcoa, Tenn. CC Case -- Not Filed, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Public Relations [folder 1 of 3], 1973 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Public Relations [folder 2 of 3], 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Public Relations [folder 3 of 3], 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Rochester Archdiocese, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Savings Bank Plan [folder 1 of 4], 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Savings Bank Plan [folder 2 of 4], 1973 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Savings Bank Plan [folder 3 of 4], 1973 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Savings Bank Plan [folder 4 of 4], 1972 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Savings Bank Plan, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Savings Actions [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Savings Actions [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Affidavits, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 5th CA 73-2950, 73-1774, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. San Antonio, Texas 23-CB-1337, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Victoria, Texas 23-CB-1333, 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. El Paso, Texas Miguel Rey 28-CA-2634, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. El Paso, Texas 28-CB-727, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 23CP-78 & 23CP-83, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  2-22-74
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Masons Department Store Case no.14-CC-855 [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Masons Department Store Case no.14-CC-855 [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Masons Department Store Case no.14-CC-855, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. San Antonio, Texas 23-CP-78 [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. San Antonio, Texas 23-CP-78 [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case No. 23-CP-83, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 23-CP-78 & 23-CP-83, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case No. 23-CA-4890, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case No. 23-CB-754, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case no.19-CC-647, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. San Antonio 23-CB-1282, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case No. 23-RM-292, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Complaint - Case No. 23-CB-1331, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case No. 23-CB-1331, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. San Antonio, Texas Case No. 23-CB-1331 [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. San Antonio, Texas Case No. 23-CB-1331 [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case 23-CB-1331, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. San Antonio Roger Castro 23-CB-4520, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- ACWA & Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case No. 28-CE-15, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- ACWA and Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case No. 28-CC-472, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 28CB 701, 733,757, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. C.B. Resumption, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. El Paso, Texas 28-CB-701, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Amalgamated Clothing of America El Paso Joint Board, ACWA 28-CB-757, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. El Paso Joint Board Case No. 28-CB-798, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 28-CB-701 28-CB-733 28-CB-757 Complaint, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. (Amended Charge) Cases No. 28-CB-701 28-CB-733, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. El Paso Joint Board 28-CB-757 (Duplicate File #1), 1973 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Bill of Particulars 28-CB-701 28-CB-733 28-CB-757, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  6/14/1973
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 28-CB-701 28-CB-733 28-CB-757, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. General 28-CB-701,733,757, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. CB-701 Settlement Issue, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case No. 28-CB-701,733,757, 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. NLRB Case No. 28-CA-2036, 1971-1973 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case No. 28-CA-2577-1 to 21, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Cutting 28-RC-2054, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  June 1972
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. El Paso, Texas 28-CA-2636 28-CA-2637 [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. El Paso, Texas 28-CA-2636 28-CA-2637 [folder 2 of 2], 1972 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case No. 28-CA-2869, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 28-CC-462, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Arrest, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Back-Pay, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. (Bat) Attorneys Conference, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Boycott Civic Material, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Farah Boycott Labor, 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Retail Boycott, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Court of Appeals, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Demonstrations, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Farah Fact Sheet, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Finer's Case no.31-CC-403, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Harold Mayer Productions, Inc., 1973-1975 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Research Materials, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Retail Stores, 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Stockholders Derivative Action, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Truck Assault, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 20-CC-1338, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case no.20-CC-1338, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case no.28-CA-3058, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case no.28-CB-593, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case no.28-CP-131, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Case no.28-RM-310, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 5th Circuit Case no.73-2128 Formal Settlement, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. El Paso Joint Board v. Farah, Lewis, & Jarvis 5th Circuit [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. El Paso Joint Board v. Farah, Lewis, & Jarvis 5th Circuit [folder 2 of 2], 1972 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 5th Circuit Case No. 73-2092 [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 5th Circuit Case No. 73-2092 [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 1973 Appeal 8th Circuit Webster 73-1184 [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 1973 Appeal 8th Circuit Webster 73-1184 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 5th Circuit Court of Appeals, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. El Paso, Texas Arrest & Malicious Prosecution, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. CC-Rayburn's Men's Wear El Paso, Texas, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. El Paso, Texas Bargaining-Cutting no.28-CA-2735, 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. El Paso, Texas - General [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  January 1972 to December 1973
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. El Paso, Texas - General [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  January 1972-December 1973
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. El Paso, Texas Litigation - Transcripts [folder 1 of 2], 1972 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. El Paso, Texas Litigation - Transcripts [folder 2 of 2], 1972 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. El Paso, Texas State Court Injunction, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. El Paso, Texas Case no.28-CC-419, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. San Antonio Texas Litigations, 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. San Antonio Texas Representation Hearing 23-RC-3826, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. San Antonio Texas Litigation Case no.23-CA-4520 [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1975 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. San Antonio Texas Litigation Case no.23-CA-4520 [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Victoria, Texas, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Victoria, Texas Case no.23-CA-4389 [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1975 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Victoria, Texas Case no.23-CA-4389 [folder 2 of 2], 1972 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. 5th Circuit - Court of Appeals Victoria, Texas 73-2369 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Victoria, Texas Litigation, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Victoria, Texas Case no.23-CA-4389 & 73-2369 [folder 1 of 3], 1973 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Victoria, Texas Case no.23-CA-4389 & 73-2369 [folder 2 of 3], 1973 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Victoria, Texas Case no.23-CA-4389 & 73-2369 [folder 3 of 3], 1973 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan [folder 1 of 2], 1954 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan [folder 2 of 2], 1954 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan [folder 1 of 2], 1959 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan [folder 2 of 2], 1959 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Capital Joint Board Building Application - NPA, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- I.R.S 85-15% (1 of 2), 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- I.R.S 85-15% (2 of 2), 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- ACWA Bylaws, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- ACWA - Salaries, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO No-Raid (Memorandum File) (1 of 2), 1963-1968 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO No-Raid (Memorandum File) (2 of 2), 1959-1963 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board David J. Monas Scholarship Program, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  2/1969
- Hicks-Ponder Company (Arizona) [folder 1 of 3], 1969-1974 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Hicks-Ponder Company (Arizona) [folder 2 of 3], 1968 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Hicks-Ponder Company (Arizona) [folder 3 of 3], 1967 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Rutter - Rex Mfg. Co., Inc. [folder 1 of 3], 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Rutter - Rex Mfg. Co., Inc. [folder 3 of 3], 1963 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Rutter - Rex Mfg. Co., Inc. [folder 3 of 3], 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Local 169 Bylaws, 1959-1961 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Local 169 Washable Fund Correspondence, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Local 169 Infant & Juvenile Manufacturer's Association, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Local 169 (Negotiations) Infant & Juvenile Manufacturer's Association Inc., 1953-1966 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Local 169 Washable Clothing Trust Agreement, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Local 169 Washable Fund Minutes, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  Oct. 11, 1962
- Local 169 Washable Fund Minutes Approved by Trustees, 1961-1963 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Local 169 Washable Fund (Signed Minutes) Minutes of Meeting of Trustees, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  March 26, 1964
- Local 169 Washable Fund Minutes of Meeting of Trustees, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Local 169 Washable Fund Extra Copies of Trustees Meeting, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  12/21/1964
- Local 169 Washable Fund Trustees Signed Minutes, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Local 169 Washable Fund Minutes of Meeting of Trustees, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  October 26, 1965
- Local 169 Washable Fund Resignations & Resolutions of Appointment, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Local 169 Washable Fund Resolutions, 1957-1961 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Local 169 Washable Fund Trust Agreement, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Local 169 Washable Fund New York State Filings [folder 1 of 5], 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Local 169 Washable Fund New York State Filings [folder 2 of 5], 1966-1968 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Local 169 Washable Fund New York State Filings [folder 3 of 5], 1968-1971 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Local 169 Washable Fund New York State Filings [folder 4 of 5], 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Local 169 Washable Fund New York State Filings [folder 5 of 5], 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Local 169 Washable Fund [folder 1 of 7], 1965 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Local 169 Washable Fund [folder 2 of 7], 1965 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Local 169 Washable Fund [folder 3 of 7], 1965 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Local 169 Washable Fund [folder 4 of 7], 1965 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Local 169 Washable Fund [folder 5 of 7], 1968 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Local 169 Washable Fund [folder 6 of 7], 1965 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Local 169 Washable Fund [folder 7 of 7], 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  6/6/1966 Volume I Pages 1-160
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  6/7/1966 Volume II Pages 161-410
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  6/8/1966 Volume III Pages 411-627
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  6/14/66 Volume VII Pages 1034-1189
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc.`, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  6/17/1966 Volume X Pages 1525-1680
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  6/22/1966 Volume XIII 2380-2590
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  6/23/1966 Volume XIV Pages 2591-2789
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  7/11/1966 Volume XVI Pages 2947-3148
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  7/12/1966 Volume XVII Pages 3149-3304a
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  7/13/1966 Volume XVIII Pages 3305-3322
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  7/14/1966 Volume XIX Pages 3323-3504
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  7/15/1966 Volume XX Pages 3305-3537
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  8/3/1966 Volume XXI Pages 3538-3699
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  8/4/1966 Volume XXII Pages 3700-3794
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  8/5/1966 Pages 4264-4484
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  8/8/1966 Volume XXIV Pages 3964-4263
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  8/9/1966 Volume XXVI Pages 4485-4662
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  8/10/1966 Volume XXVI Pages 4663-4802
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  8/11/1966 Volume XXVI Pages 4663-4802
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  8/12/1966 Volume XXVII Pages 4803-4952
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  9/6/1966 Volume XXIX Pages 4953-5130
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  9/8/1966 Volume XXXI Pages 5304-5489
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  9/13/1966 Volume XXXIV Pages 5701-5846
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  9/14/1966 Volume XXXV Pages 5848-5941
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  9/21/1966 Volume XXXVI Pages 5942-6090
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  9/22/1966 Volume XXXVII Pages 6091-6226
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  9/23/1966 Volume XXXVIII Pages 6227-6351
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  9/26/1966 Volume XXXIX Pages 6352-6488
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  9/27/1966 Volume XXXX Pages 6489-6623
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  9/28/1966 Volume XXXXI Pages 6624-6777
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  9/29/1966 Volume XXXXII Pages 6778-6830
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1967 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  2/6/1967 Volume XLIII Pages 6831-7039
- NLRB Block-Southland Sportswear Inc., Southland Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1967 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  2/7/1967 Volume 44 Pages 7040-7195
- Shutzer Mfg. Co. Inc., 1953 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Shutzer, Barry, & Durant General File [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1966 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Shutzer, Barry, & Durant General File [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1962 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Pittsburgh Joint Board Staff Retirement Plan [folder 1 of 2], 1966-1972 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Pittsburgh Joint Board Staff Retirement Plan [folder 2 of 2], 1965 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan, 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 6)